<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
<topics>
<topic>
<topic>
<id>001</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Having Beers in a Bar</title>
<description>Find the moment in 2015 and 2016 when u1 enjoyed
beers in the bar.</description>
<narrative>To be considered relevant, u1 must be clearly in a
bar. Any moments that u1 drinks beers at home or outside without
the bar view are not considered relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>002</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Building Personal Computer</title>
<description>Find the moment when u1 built my personal
computer from scratch.</description>
<narrative>To be considered relevant, u1 must be clearly at
the office with the PC parts on the table. Any moments that the u1
is not in the office or there are no PC parts/uncompleted PCs on
the table are not considered relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>003</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>In A Toy Shop</title>
<description>Find the moment when u1 was looking at items in
a toyshop.</description>
<narrative>To be considered relevant, u1 must be clearly in a
toyshop. Various toys are being examined, such as electronic
trains, model kits and board games. Being in an electronics store,
or a supermarket, are not considered to be relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>004</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Television Recording</title>
<description>Find the moments when u1 was being recorded for
a television show.</description>
<narrative>To be considered relevant, there must clearly be a
television camera in front of u1. The moments the
interviewer/cameramen is interviewing/recording u1 are also
considered relevant. This can take place at home or in another
location. All recording took place in one day and in more than one
location.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>005</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Public Transport In Home Country</title>
<description>Find the moments in 2015 and 2018 when u1 was
using public transports in my home country
(Ireland).</description>
<narrative>Taking any form of public transport in Ireland is
considered relevant, such as bus, taxi, train and boat. The
moments that u1 is driving a car is not relevant</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>006</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Seaside Moments</title>
<description>Find moment(s) in which u1 was walking by the
sea taking photos or eating ice cream.</description>
<narrative>To be considered relevant, u1 must be taking a
walk by the sea or eating ice cream and the sea is clearly
visible. u1 must also be shown taking a photo with his/her camera
phone or holding the ice cream cone at this time. On the beach or
walking on a pier are both considered relevant once u1 is taking a
photo or eating ice cream.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>007</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Grocery Stores</title>
<description>Find moment(s) in 2016 and 2018 when u1 was
grocery shopping on the weekends.</description>
<narrative>To be considered relevant, u1 must be clearly in a
grocery shop and buy something from it. Any moments on Saturdays
and Sundays when u1 was in a grocery store and visibly interacting
with products are also considered relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>008</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Photograph of The Bridge</title>
<description>Find the moment when u1 was taking a photo of a
bridge.</description>
<narrative>Moments when u1 was walking on a street without
stopping to take a photo of a bridge are not relevant. Any other
moment showing a bridge when a photo was not being taken are also
not considered to be relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>009</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Car Repair</title>
<description>Find the moment when u1 was repairing his car in
the garden.</description>
<narrative>Moments when u1 was repairing his car in the
garden with the gloves on his hand. Sometimes, he also held the
hammer and his phone and these moments are also considered
relevant. The moments when u1 was with the cars without showing
repair action are not considered relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic>
<id>010</id>
<uid>u1</uid>
<title>Monsters</title>
<description>Find the moment(s) when u1 was looking at an old
clock, with flowers visible, with a small monster watching
u1.</description>
<narrative>Moments when u1 was at home, looking at an old
clock, with flowers visible, with a lamp and perhaps two small
monsters watching u1 are considered relevant. One of the monsters
might be a long rabbit. The moments without one of the
aforementioned conditions: monsters, flowers, and old clock are
not considered relevant.</narrative>
</topic>